virgingaming.com 2014-02-18

# Privacy Policy for Virgin Gaming

## Website Privacy Policy

(last modified: January 15, 2013)

Virgin Gaming recognizes that your privacy is serious business and we are committed to protecting your personal information. This website Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes the types of information collected about you when you visit the VirginGaming.com website (the "Site"), how that information may be used, when it may be disclosed, how you can take steps to control the use and disclosure of your personal information, and how that information is protected by us. 

In this Privacy Policy, which is available via a link at the bottom of every page on the Site, "we", "us" and "our" means Intertaintech Corporation, as well as its affiliates on its behalf, including Impact Entertainment LLC (collectively, "Virgin Gaming"). Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.virgingaming.com/web/termsandconditions) of service (the "T&Cs"). 

Key Definitions 

  * "Personal Information" - generally means information about you as an identifiable individual, but excludes business contact information, specific publicly available information, and Gamer Information. 
  * "Gamer Information" means information about activity on the Site by you as a member which is not itself personally identifiable with you and is therefore not Personal Information, but which may be linked (on a non-identifiable basis) to your account information, and includes your (a) Username or Alias, (b) Skill Rating, (c) Top Players Ranking (if any) and Virgin Gaming Points balance, (d) scores in games and tournaments, (e) gaming preferences and personal motto, (f) summary of gaming activity, including when you joined, and the number of games that you have played, (g) winnings from games and tournament, and (h) footage of gameplay in promotional materials such as trailers which may be displayed on the Site, or on website run by other parties including those of our marketing partners (for example, "play of the week", "highlight reel" or similar content). 

This Privacy Policy applies to the Personal Information of all "users" of the Site, including unregistered visitors and "members" who have registered and maintain an account on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information collected through any other website operated by third parties, such as linked websites operated by sponsors, advertisers or game developers. 

This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect with respect to your Personal Information which we retain for a limited period of time after your use or participation in the Site or any particular Service, tournament or game offered through the Site terminates or ceases, or is suspended or deactivated for any reason, in order to ensure that you may easily restart gameplay at a later time. In any case, should you continue to be an inactive player for more than a reasonable time period, Virgin Gaming will delete your personal information. 

If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the Site or any of the activities or Services offered through the Site. 

Finally, this Privacy Policy explains how we manage and safeguard Personal Information in the course of operating our business. We are dedicated to adhering to the following principles that relate to the collection, use, retention and disclosure of Personal Information. 

### 1\. ACCOUNTABILITY

Virgin Gaming is accountable for all Personal Information in its control. This includes information under the direct control of Virgin Gaming, as well as Personal Information that Virgin Gaming may transfer to its affiliates or to third party service providers, in each case for the purposes of (i) performing support functions, such as payment processing, business analytics, customer support, printing and mailing, data storage and destruction, and (ii) marketing any of Virgin Gaming's products and services. Virgin Gaming will use contractual or other measures to require third parties that process information or provide services on our behalf to maintain a level of privacy protection comparable to our own practices. 

Numerous individuals within Virgin Gaming are responsible for the day-to-day collection and processing of Personal Information, including technical and administration personnel trained for this purpose. However, Virgin Gaming has a designated Privacy Officer who is responsible for Virgin Gaming's compliance with applicable privacy legislation. Any questions or concerns with regard to the manner in which Virgin Gaming handles or manages Personal Information, or in respect of this Privacy Policy should be directed to our Privacy Officer who can be reached as follows: 

Virgin Gaming Privacy Officer  
Email: [privacy@virgingaming.com](mailto:privacy@virgingaming.com)

### 2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

#### A. What information is collected through the sites?

##### Types of Information

We collect two types of information from you when you visit the Site: information that does not identify you personally ("Non-Personal Information"); and Personal Information, as defined in more detail above). 

###### (i) Non-Personal Information

As examples of Non-Personal Information, we collect: 

  * through our Web servers, automatic recordings of certain technical information related to your visit to the Site. This information is anonymous and does not identify you personally. It includes things such as: the Internet domain for your Internet service provider; the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer accessing the Site; the address of the last webpage that you visited prior to clicking through to the Site; the browser used and the type of computer operating system that your computer is using; information about your computer hardware; the date and time that you visited the Site; and a record of which pages you viewed while you were visiting the Site; 
  * demographic information which does not identify an individual; and 
  * Gamer Information. 

###### (ii) Personal Information

We collect Personal Information as follows: 

(a) _Initial Registration:_ from you, in connection with completing the "one step registration" required for you to create a free, basic user account (a "Basic Account"): 

  1. your email address for the purpose of (A) verifying your identity by emailing you, (B) you logging in, (C) marketing upcoming game tournaments to you, and (D) emailing game results to you; 
  2. your date of birth, for the purpose of ensuring that you are permitted to create an account based upon your age, 
  3. where you reside, for the purpose of ensuring that you are permitted to create an account based upon your jurisdiction, and 
  4. you user name, for the purpose of identifying you. 

(collectively, the "Basic Information"). 

(b) _Deposit Funds into the Basic Account:_ from you, for the purpose of creating and depositing funds to the your Basic Account which will allow the Individual to enter cash games and tournaments (a "Real Money Account"), in addition to the Basic Information: 

  1. your first name and last name; 
  2. the following information with respect to your credit card: type, number, expiration month, expiration year and card verification number; and 
  3. the following billing information: your street address, city, postal code, province and country. 

(c) _Withdraw funds from Real Money Account:_ from you, for the purpose of confirming your identity: 

  1. your Paypal email address, first name, last name; and 
  2. your street address, city, postal code, province and country, and phone number. 

(d) _Withdraw funds from Real Money Account and Claim Prizing:_ from Individuals, for the purpose of confirming their identity: 

  1. Name, photograph, age and address (via a copy of your driver's license or utility bill); 

(e) _Edit profile:_ from you, for the purpose of updating your contact information, your "site information", your password, and your communication preferences: 

  1. your first name, last name, Individual's street address, city, postal code, province and country; 
  2. your time zone; your avatar; and your PlayStation Network ID and XBOX Live Gamertag (in order for you to make or accept game challenges, and for us to track your game results; 
  3. in response to our "About you" query, a sentence about the Individual for the purpose of the Individual's profile; 
  4. your old and new password; and 
  5. your communication preferences. 

(f) _Game challenges (on first challenge):_ from you, your PlayStation Network ID and XBOX Live Gamertag, and Electronic Arts email address, in order to make or accept game challenges, and for us to track your game results 

The Site also provide you with certain ways to voluntarily give us your Personal Information, as follows: 

  1. from social network sites ("SNS"), where you decide to create an account by logging into a SNS via the Site, certain Personal Information which you have provided the SNS (for example, the name, email address and other Personal Information which the Individual has made publicly available via the SNS, in each case depending on the privacy settings of the Individual on the SNS), for the purpose of completing the opening of the account. For example, see below for details for when you join by Facebook;
  2. from you, through your interaction with the Site (for example, information about which games were played, player rating information and player game statistics); 
  3. from you, through your completion of contest forms or other participation in promotional efforts, for the purpose of such contests and promotions, including for the purpose of awarding prizes;
  4. from you, through your completion of surveys, for the purpose of gathering your opinions and comments in regard to Virgin Gaming's products and services;
  5. from you, through using links contained on the Site to send Virgin Gaming an email message which contains such information, for the purpose identified at the point of collection on the Site;
  6. from you, to the extent that you post content with such Personal Information to chat windows, user fora or similar fora on the Site, for the purpose of each such forum; and
  7. from you, to the extent that you provide Personal Information when you contact Virgin Gaming's Customer Care representatives via live chat or email.
  8. from you, through you voluntarily disclosing information about yourself when you use the "Invite Your Friends / Tell-A-Friend" feature, for the purpose of inviting others to create Basic Accounts or Real Money Accounts;
  9. about other individuals who are identified as your "friends", in the form of the names and e-mail addresses of your friends when you use the "Invite Your Friends / Tell-A-Friend" feature on the Site, for the purpose of inviting others to create Basic Accounts or Real Money Accounts; 

In order to provide a fair playing environment for all users and to protect the integrity of the Site, we also collect Personal Information which we use to investigate complaints of cheating or behavior that we believe may be contrary to the T&Cs, including the Rules of Conduct. This may include screenshots of players' computer desktops or footage of in-game play. 

In addition to collecting Personal Information directly from visitors to the Site, we may also collect Personal Information from third parties such as marketing partners to which permission has been granted to share that information with us. 

When you download any Virgin Gaming Widget or a Virgin Gaming application, you may also be provided with the opportunity to download software provided by parties other than Virgin Gaming (for example, Xfire from Xfire, Inc.). Please note that when you install and use software provided by third parties, any information that you provide through such use (including Personal Information) will be subject to the privacy policy of that software provider, and not this Privacy Policy. 

###### Facebook Connect

You can register to join Virgin Gaming via the Site or by logging into your account with certain SNS (i.e., Facebook) via our Site. If you decide to create your Account by logging into a SNS via the Site, we will extract the Personal Information you have provided to the SNS (such as your "real" name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) from the account you have with such SNS and use that information to create your account; the information we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS. For example, our Service allows users to create an account and login to the Service using their Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you are not currently registered as a Member and you click on "Sign in Using Facebook", you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join Virgin Gaming. By using Facebook Connect, you are allowing Virgin Gaming to access your Facebook account information for the purpose of completing your registration as a Member of Virgin Gaming, and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Service via Facebook. 

#### B. What are "cookies" and how does the Site use them?

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred (through your browser) from a website to the hard drive of your computer. The cookie identifies your browser but will not let a website know any Personal Information about you, such as your name or address. These files are then used by such websites as a kind of electronic identification tag when users revisit that site. Since cookies are only text files, they cannot run on your computer, search your computer for other information, or transmit any information to anyone. 

As with many major websites, the Site use cookies. Cookies are used by the Site so that we can recognize you when you return to the Site and personalize your settings and preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you wish, you can change your browser settings either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. 

#### C. Personal Information about Children

Our Site is intended for a general audience and we do not knowingly (a) allow people under 18 years of age to create accounts on the Site and (b) collect Personal Information from people under 18 years of age through our Site. In addition, in the event that a visitor to our Site identifies himself or herself as a person under the age of 18, we will not collect, store or use any Personal Information of such individual. In the event that we receive Personal Information that we discover was provided by a person under the age of 18, we will promptly delete all such Personal Information not required for purpose of continuing to block such person's use of the Site, and will comply with applicable laws, including, as applicable, the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

#### D. Limits to Collecting Personal Information

We limit the type of mandatory information collected by us. We collect only the Personal Information that is required for the purposes described in the following paragraphs under the heading "Use and Disclosure of Personal Information" below (the "Purposes"). 

### 3\. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use and disclose your information for the following purposes.

#### A. Internal Uses

We collect, use and disclose your Personal Information for such purposes to which you consent at the time of collection or in any case prior to such use, and as otherwise permitted or required by applicable law, including: 

  * to operate our Site; to open and maintain your customer accounts with us, deposit funds into such accounts, and withdraw funds from such accounts; to edit your profile; and for the purpose of game challenges, in each case as more particularly described above; 
  * to provide a product or service requested by you; 
  * to contact you regarding updates to the Site, your account status, our new products and services and upcoming events, changes to our products and services; 
  * to collect subscription and entry fees from you and to process payments; 
  * for promotional or related purposes without additional compensation, including with respect to tournaments and the awarding of prizes; 
  * to prevent fraud and protect the integrity of the Site; 
  * to deliver prizes to you; and 
  * to ensure that you comply with the T&Cs (including in order to facilitate a fair gameplay environment) and are permitted to create an account based upon your age and where you reside. 
  * to, in our discretion, use Personal Information to contact you regarding changes to the T&Cs and any other policies or agreements relevant to the Site, including this Privacy Policy. 

Also, if you use the "Invite Your Friends / Tell-A-Friend" feature, we will use the name and e-mail address that you provides to invite your friend to create a user account. 

When you create your account and when we collect your Personal Information, you can customize these preferences. If you wish to change your account preferences to modify the ways that we contact you, please contact Customer Care or, in the case where we use your Personal Information to communicate with you via email, use the "unsubscribe" link included in all email messages sent on our behalf. 

#### B. Related Entities and Authorized Third-Party Service Providers

In addition to sharing information between entities comprising the Virgin Gaming group for the Purposes, and in order to better serve our customers, we may transfer Personal Information to third-party service providers who are legally or contractually obligated to only use the information to help us provide our Services and not for any other purpose. For example, Virgin Gaming uses outside contractors for the purposes of (i) performing support functions, such as payment processing, business analytics, customer support, printing and mailing, data storage and destruction, and (ii) marketing any of Virgin Gaming's products and services. 

From time to time such Virgin Gaming group entities and third parties may hold, use or disclose your Personal Information outside of Canada, and while outside of Canada such Personal Information may be accessed by regulatory authorities pursuant to the laws of such other jurisdictions. 

These third parties may be located in the United States, Canada or elsewhere. 

#### C. Co-Branded Partners

Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom Virgin Gaming may jointly offer a Service or feature, such as a Tournament. You can tell when you are accessing a Service offered by a Co-Branded Partner because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a Service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. In doing so, you may be providing your Personal Information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or, with your consent, we may share your Personal Information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may apply to its use of your Personal Information. 

#### D. Marketing Partners

To the consent that you consent, we may also disclose Personal Information you provide us to third party marketing partners who provide products, information or services you have expressly requested or which we believe you may be interested in purchasing or obtaining, in order that they may provide you with information regarding such products, information or services. In doing so, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that these third parties only use the Personal Information for our stated Purposes and that they provide a method of opting out from receiving future communications from such parties, but we shall not otherwise be responsible for their handling or dissemination practices with respect to Personal Information. If you subsequently wish to change your account preferences to not receive information from such third party marketing partners, please contact Customer Care or use the "unsubscribe" link included in email messages sent by such parties. 

#### E. Legal Compliance

There may be instances when Virgin Gaming may disclose Personal Information without providing notice or choice, as required or permitted by applicable laws, which may include (i) where required pursuant to a subpoena, other form of legal process or request on behalf of any local, provincial, state, or federal governmental department or agency; (ii) in an emergency, to protect the safety and physical security of users of the Services or members of the public; or (iii) to investigate breaches of agreements or Canadian law. 

#### F. Business Transfers

If Virgin Gaming sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Virgin Gaming may transfer your Personal Information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. 

### 4\. OBTAINING CONSENT

In most cases, when we do collect Personal Information directly from an individual, the Purposes for which the individual provides us with the information - for example, as required for us to effectively provide our Services - will be clear, and as such, consent to the collection and use of Personal Information for those Purposes will be implied by use of the Services. If we choose to use Personal Information already in our possession for a purpose that was not identified at the time we initially collected the information, we will seek the consent of the affected individuals before using this information for the new purpose. Please note that if the new purpose is required or permitted by law, Virgin Gaming is not required to seek the consent of the affected individuals and may not do so. Individuals may withdraw consent to the collection, use and disclosure of their Personal Information at any time, subject to certain restrictions set out in applicable privacy legislation, but should recognize that by doing so they may be unable to utilize the Services and products offered on the Site. When a member uses the "Invite Your Friends / Tell-A-Friend" feature, we rely on that individual to obtain the consent of their friend to allow us to use that information to invite them to create a user account. 

### 5\. MANAGEMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Virgin Gaming has policies and procedures as to how long it retains information that it collects. Personal Information that is no longer required to fulfill the Purposes is either destroyed, erased or rendered anonymous to prevent unauthorized parties from gaining access to the information. 

We retain Personal Information received from third parties in accordance with our legal and contractual obligations. The file containing your Personal Information will be made available to the authorized employees, contractors or agents of Virgin Gaming who need to access the information in connection with the Purposes, and will be held primarily in an electronic database. 

Personal Information included in computer databases is typically stored in a secure data center with an extra copy of the data stored at an alternate location of equal security to ensure that we will be able to retrieve the data even in the event of a disaster. These computer databases may be located in Canada, the United States or elsewhere in the world. From time to time, we may transfer Personal Information stored in these databases (as otherwise permitted under this Privacy Policy) to third-party service providers located in Canada, the United States or elsewhere in the world. For example, certain third-party service providers such as data storage companies, computer security specialists, database technicians, or corporate affiliates of Virgin Gaming may have remote access to Personal Information in our custody for the purposes described herein, but we use contractual and other safeguards to ensure that Personal Information transferred to such parties is provided with a comparable level of protection as Virgin Gaming provides, regardless of the format in which the information exists. 

Virgin Gaming has implemented a variety of commercially reasonable security safeguards to protect Personal Information in our control against loss, theft, misuse and interception by third parties. These safeguards include organizational, technical and physical measures designed to protect information from unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Among the steps taken are: 

  * premises security;
  * restricted file access to Personal Information;
  * technology safeguards, including security software, firewalls to prevent hacking and other unauthorized computer access; and
  * internal password and security policies.

However, please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We are committed to protecting your Personal information, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Please take reasonable steps to guard against identity theft, including 'phishing' attacks. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. In the event of unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, you must notify Virgin Gaming immediately and promptly change your password. 

### 6\. ACCURACY AND CURRENCY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Virgin Gaming is committed to open and fair privacy practices which comply with applicable privacy legislation. 

Any individual may request access to their Personal Information held by Virgin Gaming by contacting Virgin Gaming's Privacy Officer in writing. After receiving such a request, our Privacy Officer shall inform the individual of the existence, use and disclosure of their Personal Information and shall allow the individual to access such information. 

In certain circumstances to the extent permitted or required by applicable law, access to Personal Information may be denied. If we deny an individual's request for access to their Personal Information, we will advise such individual in writing of the reason for the refusal and they may then challenge our decision. 

Where Personal Information is used on an on-going basis, Virgin Gaming undertakes to correct any information that is shown to be inaccurate, incomplete or not up-to-date. Otherwise, Virgin Gaming does not routinely update Personal Information. It is the member's responsibility to provide us current, complete, truthful and accurate information, including Personal Information, and to keep such information up to date. We cannot and will not be responsible for any problems or liability that may arise if a member does not provide us with accurate, truthful or complete information or Personal Information or the member fails to update such information or Personal Information 

Upon notification from an individual of their desire to have any or all of their Personal Information in our records deleted or destroyed, Virgin Gaming may undertake to delete or destroy all such information to the extent that retention of such information is not required or permitted by applicable law, such as for the investigation of claims or the defense of an action, and some Personal Information may remain in back-up storage for this purpose. In the event that an individual wishes to challenge Virgin Gaming's compliance with any of these principles, they can contact Virgin Gaming's Privacy Officer using the contact information set out at the outset of this Privacy Policy. If Virgin Gaming finds a complaint to be justified, appropriate measures will be taken, including, if necessary, amending our policies and practices. 

### 7\. GOVERNING

The Site is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the Province of Ontario and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein, without regard to its conflict of law provisions, and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of and venue in the courts of the Province of Ontario located in Toronto, Ontario, Canada, in all disputes arising out of or relating to the Services. Notwithstanding any other provisions of this Policy or the T&Cs, we may seek injunctive or other equitable relief from any court of competent jurisdiction. You agree that any dispute that cannot be resolved between the parties shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action. 

We make no representation that this Site is operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of, or governed by, other nations. By utilizing the Services and participating in Site activities, you certify that you meet the age and other eligibility requirements for the Site and the Services set forth in the T&Cs. If you do not meet the age and other eligibility requirements, please discontinue using the Site and the Services immediately as your continued use of the Site and the Services indicates that you are agreeing to the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### 8\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

All policies and procedures of Virgin Gaming are reviewed and updated periodically to reflect changes in our practices and Services, including this Privacy Policy. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will update the "effective Date" and such changes will be effective upon posting to the Site, to the extent that such changes do not require that we first obtain your consent to same. 

Copyright © 2013 Virgin Gaming - All Rights Reserved
